

# **OBJECTIVES**

A proficient professional with a clear goal to ensure continuous learning for developing professional career path and to get those opportunities form this organization an expert that my ability and skills will be useful for the organization.

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Date Of Birth: 25 DEC 1991 Marital: Single Nationality: Myanmar

Gender: Male
Passport: ME289105
Date of Issue 01 JUN 2019
Date of Exp: 31 May 2024
Language: English, Myanmar

#### CONTACT

#### **Phone**

+959799623994

## WhatsApp

+959799623994

#### **Email**

ehderlel@gmail.com

#### Facebook

https://www.facebook.com/ehdarler

No.(499) SAKAWAR Street, PATHEIN, Ayeyarwady, Myanmar

# SAW EH DAR LER

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University Of PATHEIN**

2014 - 2017

Bachelor of Arts (English), University of PATHEIN

#### JDC

2017 - 2018 One Stop Java Course (JDC) Java developer class Certificate

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# [MSI] [Internet Café Service]

2014-2015

Worked as Internet Café service at MSI

#### [World Vision] [Data Entry]

2015-2016

Worked in NGO for data entry, part time

#### [OPM] [Software Programmer]

2018 - 2019

Worked in software company as programmer.

# **SKILLS**

